[
  {
    "question": "What is 221 \u00f7 17?",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 9?",
    "answer": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 68 - 68?",
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 56?",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 24?",
    "answer": "216"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 + 96?",
    "answer": "107"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 5?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 8?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 16?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 88?",
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 76?",
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 89 - 92?",
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 85 \u00f7 17?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 7?",
    "answer": "133"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 100 \u00f7 20?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 66 - 7?",
    "answer": "59"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 116?",
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 + 54?",
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 70 \u00f7 14?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 3?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 - 21?",
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 - 45?",
    "answer": "-22"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 160?",
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 16?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 14?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 96 + 3?",
    "answer": "99"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 29?",
    "answer": "841"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 8?",
    "answer": "136"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 1?",
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 14?",
    "answer": "280"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 + 55?",
    "answer": "82"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 86 - 96?",
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 + 63?",
    "answer": "82"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 36 - 81?",
    "answer": "-45"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 35 + 24?",
    "answer": "59"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 114 \u00f7 19?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 10?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 128?",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 18?",
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 41 - 24?",
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 68 - 95?",
    "answer": "-27"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 20 - 52?",
    "answer": "-32"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 10?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 2?",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 216 \u00f7 18?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 86 + 93?",
    "answer": "179"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 49 - 70?",
    "answer": "-21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 11?",
    "answer": "319"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 + 82?",
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 120 \u00f7 10?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 28?",
    "answer": "700"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 4?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 99 \u00f7 9?",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 224 \u00f7 16?",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 72?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 \u00f7 1?",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 27?",
    "answer": "621"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 30 - 32?",
    "answer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 17?",
    "answer": "221"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 - 96?",
    "answer": "-48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 32 + 53?",
    "answer": "85"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 53 + 15?",
    "answer": "68"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 19?",
    "answer": "114"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 94 - 47?",
    "answer": "47"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 210 \u00f7 15?",
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 - 74?",
    "answer": "-35"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 8?",
    "answer": "208"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 58 + 78?",
    "answer": "136"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 280 \u00f7 14?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 53 + 51?",
    "answer": "104"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 144?",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 260 \u00f7 13?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 9?",
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 \u00f7 3?",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 37?",
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10 \u00f7 10?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 187 \u00f7 11?",
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 + 19?",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 73 - 1?",
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 14?",
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 84?",
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 114 \u00f7 19?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 306 \u00f7 17?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 68?",
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 25?",
    "answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 306 \u00f7 17?",
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 4?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 26?",
    "answer": "442"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 8?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 18 - 22?",
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 9?",
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 20?",
    "answer": "540"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 21 - 67?",
    "answer": "-46"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 12?",
    "answer": "228"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 4?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 112 \u00f7 16?",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 27?",
    "answer": "135"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 19 - 32?",
    "answer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 21 + 95?",
    "answer": "116"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 16?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 196?",
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 44?",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 168?",
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 8?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 20 + 68?",
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 57 + 18?",
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 23?",
    "answer": "322"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 84 - 83?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 12?",
    "answer": "324"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 62 - 87?",
    "answer": "-25"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 26?",
    "answer": "624"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 16?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 6?",
    "answer": "138"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 4?",
    "answer": "116"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1 \u00d7 23?",
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 54 + 77?",
    "answer": "131"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 35 + 35?",
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 14?",
    "answer": "308"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 23?",
    "answer": "207"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 1?",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 - 38?",
    "answer": "-36"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 44 + 30?",
    "answer": "74"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 170 \u00f7 10?",
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 7?",
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 1?",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 1?",
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 39 - 46?",
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 83 + 74?",
    "answer": "157"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 160?",
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 19?",
    "answer": "266"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 192 \u00f7 12?",
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 136 \u00f7 17?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 + 48?",
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 16 - 5?",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 + 94?",
    "answer": "106"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 99 + 77?",
    "answer": "176"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 96?",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 26 - 75?",
    "answer": "-49"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 192?",
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 59 + 51?",
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 85 - 2?",
    "answer": "83"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 70 + 3?",
    "answer": "73"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 25% of 32?",
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 5?",
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 11 - 59?",
    "answer": "-48"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 4?",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 14 + 67?",
    "answer": "81"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 58 - 85?",
    "answer": "-27"
  }
]